Please take a short break.
少し休憩してください
copper
どう
Did you do it?
した の?
copper
どう
Did you do it?
した の?
Are you crying?
泣いてるの?
it hurts?
痛い?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Please tell me the reason.
理由を言ってください
what happened?
どうしたの?
why are you crying?
なんで泣いてるの?
Please tell me.
言ってください
I'm getting scared...
怖くなっちゃって...
scared?
怖い?
lie?
嘘?
It looks really wet
すごい濡れてるようだって
...
Please stand behind me.
後 ろに手をついてください
It slipped out.
抜けた
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Let's do a little more.
もうちょっとやろうよ
It's okay if you don't cry that much, right?
そんなに泣かなくても大丈夫でしょ?
It's okay if you don't cry so much.
そんなに泣かなくても大丈夫だよ
Hey?
ねえ?
Since we've come this far...
ここまで来ちゃってるから...
scared.
怖い
scary scary
怖い怖い
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
scared.
怖い